<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title><![CDATA[Urban Template]]></title>
		<link>https://aulafactotum.com/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[Urban is a strong foundation for the web presence of your agency.]]></description>
		<atom:link href="https://aulafactotum.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 19:55:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[The history of marketing]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[The beginnings of digital marketing technology can be traced back to the 1980's, when computers became sophisticated enough to store huge volumes of customer information. For a brief moment, no one knew what would happen in digital marketing, but by the 90's it all became clear.]]></description>
			<link>https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-08-12-the-history-of-marketing</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-08-12-the-history-of-marketing</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Definition of sales]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[A person or organization expressing an interest in acquiring the offered item of value is referred to as a potential buyer, prospective customer or prospect. Buying and selling are understood to be two sides of the same &quot;coin&quot; or transaction. Both seller and buyer engage in a process of negotiation to consummate the exchange of values. The exchange, or selling, process has implied rules and identifiable stages.]]></description>
			<link>https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-08-06-definition-of-sales</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-08-06-definition-of-sales</guid>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Effective upselling techniques]]></title>
			<description><![CDATA[Upselling is a sales technique whereby a seller induces the customer to purchase more expensive items, upgrades or other add-ons in an attempt to make a more profitable sale. While it usually involves marketing more profitable services or products, it can be simply exposing the customer to other options that were perhaps not considered.]]></description>
			<link>https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-07-28-effective-upselling-techniques</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://aulafactotum.com/blog/2016-07-28-effective-upselling-techniques</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>